ACTWU Audio-Visual Materials 5619 AV
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- J.P. Stevens Music 1 of 5 (Box 103)
- J.P. Stevens Music 2 of 5 (Box 104)
- J.P. Stevens Music 3 of 5 (Box 105)
- J.P. Stevens Music 4 of 5 (Box 106)
- J.P. Stevens Music 5 of 5 (Box 107)
- 60 Minutes: Brown Lung -- 2/4/1979 (Box 108)
- ACTWU Convention (6/1990) (Box 109)
- Actor - Weinstein (Box 110)
- Lichtenburg Rally: Tape 1 of 2 (See Amalgamated. Life) -- (4/2/1990) (Box 111)
- Amalgamated Life (1 of 7) (Box 112)
  Tapes #1-#4 and #11-#13 -- moved from box 20 to box 11 during the reorganization of the collection
- Amalgamated Life (2 of 7) (Box 113)
- Amalgamated Life (3 of 7) - tape #3 (Box 114)
- Amalgamated Life (4 of 7) - tape #4 (Box 115)
- Amalgamated Life (5 of 7) - tape #11 (Box 116)
- Amalgamated Life (6 of 7) - tape #12 (Box 117)
- Amalgamated Life (7 of 7) - tape #13 (Box 118)
- NYS Board/Scholarship, Summer enrichment (Box 119)
- NY Joint Board / Christmas 1988 / Faces Amalgamated Service & Allied Tape #1 (Box 120)
- Vision Center / Cecil Toppin: Tape #2 (Box 121)
- Actor - A. Loevy 775 (Box 122)
- Actor / Weinstein / 2: Lewistown I (Box 123)
- Chicago / Arthur Loevy / 0-1600: NYS Board / Christmas / Rumore Sheinkman (Box 124)
- ACTWU - David Dinkins Rally / NYS Board (Box 125)
- David Dinkins (Box 126)
- Actor - Hillman: 0-2337 // Actor 2336-2914 (Box 127)
- Actor - Lewistown II: 0-2779 (Box 128)
- President Bush - Tape #2: 6/22/1989 (Box 129)
- NY Joint Board - 1989 Scholarship: 0-1140 // Hillman - President Bush Tape #1 (Box 130)
- Kenneth Balock - National President (Box 131)
- ACTWU Fighting Back (Box 132)
- ACTWU - Fighting Back (Box 133)
- ACTWU - Speech by Gregory Stevens (Box 134)
- Swaity, Paul - 11/15/1978 (tape 1 of 3) (Box 135)
- Swaity, Paul: 11/15/1978 (tape 2 of 3) (Box 136)
- Swaity, Paul - 11/15/1978 (Tape 3 of 3) (Box 137)
- Captive Audience Speech, 1973 (Box 138)
  side 1.J.P. Stevens, Waterboro, SC -- 11/19/1973//8:20 am - Speaker jack McGill-Plant Manager; side 2.J.P. Stevens, Aberdeen, NC -- 2nd Shift ---- 11/19/1973, Marvin Crow, VP Guliston Division only about 1/2 of the speech //// moved from box 23 to box 17
- K (unlabeled) (Box 139)
- First and Second Parts of speech (only Edward Kennedy) (Box 140)
- Edward Kennedy 3/3/1973 (Box 141)
- Unlabeled (Box 142)
- Hearing #1 (Box 143)
- Hearing #2 (to Mr. Paul Swaity) (Box 144)
- Unlabeled (Box 145)
- Beginning of tape (Box 146)
- OSHA 200: Hanes - South Carolina (1978-1982) (Box 147)
- Byssinosis - NBC-CBS (Box 148)
- WINS all News Radio - 4:07 pm - July 29, 1980 - J.P. Stevens / C.L. Sutton (Box 149)
- NEWS of New York - WNYC (NYC) 6:30 pm - 7/29/1980 - J.P. Stevens, C.L. Sutton (Box 150)
- NEWS WINS - 6:08 pm: 7/29/1980 -- C.L. Sutton, J.P. Stevens (Box 151)
- NEWS WINS - 7:30 pm 7-29-1980 on C.L. Sutton & J.P. Stevens (Box 152)
- NEWS WINS (NY) 11:00 pm on C.L. Sutton / 7/29/1980 / J.P. Stevens (Box 153)
- WINS all news radio: 3:36 pm - July 29, 1980 -- on J.P. Stevens & C.L. Sutton (Box 154)
- WNBC TV (NYC) 6:25 pm: 7/29/1980 -- On J.P. Stevens & C.L. Sutton (Box 155)
- NEWS - WOR T.V. - 12 Noon 7/29/1980: on C.L. Sutton, J.P. Stevens (Box 156)
- Norma Rae/ C.L. Sutton (Box 157)
- J.P. Stevens - White Horse - 1/10/1978 (Original) (Box 158)
- Speech by Gregory - Supt. - Stevens- Montgomery, Alabama: 8/16/1976 (Box 159)
- ACTWU - Speech by Gregory Stevens (Box 160)
- ACTWU - Speech by Gregory Stevens (Box 161)
- ACTWU - Speech by Gregory Stevens (Box 162)
- Crystal Lee Sutton - Community Affairs Forum (Box 163)
- Harold Mayer Productions - J.P. Stevens - White Horse (Box 164)
- Murray Finely Tribute for May 21, 1987 (Box 165)
- Hillman Funeral w/Stephen Wise, 1946 (Box 166)
- Conclusion of Hillman Health Centre project - Chicago (1955) (Box 167)
- Sidney Hillman Speeches, 1937-1946 (Box 168)
- Salute to Labor (Sept. 1941) (Box 169)
- Opening of Hillman Health Center - Chicago 1955 (pt.1) (Box 170)
- Sidney Hillman - Town Hall Meeting (6-14-1935) // Hillman Centre (pts.5-6): Bessie Hillman (Box 171)
- Video digitized from the collection. (Box 172)